{
  "user": [
    {
      "fullname": "jessie eisenberg",
      "email": "jessberg@aol.com",
      "username": "jessberg",
      "password": "jessberg123",
      "isAdmin": false,
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "fullname": "Alicia Winters",
      "email": "awinters@aol.com",
      "username": "awinters",
      "password": "awinters123",
      "isAdmin": false,
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "fullname": "Morticia Summers",
      "email": "msummers@aol.com",
      "username": "msummers",
      "password": "msummers123",
      "isAdmin": false,
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "fullname": "Mark Thomas",
      "email": "mthomas@aol.com",
      "username": "mthomas",
      "password": "mthomas123",
      "isAdmin": false,
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "fullname": "Thomas",
      "email": "Adkins",
      "username": "tadkins",
      "password": "tadkins123",
      "isAdmin": true,
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "fullname": "Tracy Jenkins",
      "email": "tjenkins@aol.com",
      "username": "tjenkins",
      "password": "tjenkins123",
      "isAdmin": false,
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "fullname": "Charlene Mathis",
      "email": "cmathis@aol.in",
      "username": "cmathis",
      "password": "Mathis123",
      "isAdmin": true,
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "fullname": "Timothy Greene",
      "email": "tgeene@aol.com",
      "username": "tgreene",
      "password": "tgreene123",
      "isAdmin": true,
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "fullname": "tester",
      "email": "tester",
      "username": "tester",
      "password": "tester",
      "isAdmin": false,
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "fullname": "tested",
      "email": "tested",
      "username": "tested",
      "password": "tested",
      "isAdmin": true,
      "id": 10
    }
  ],
  "quiz": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "HTML stands for?",
      "options": [
        "Hyper Text Markup Language",
        "High Text Markup Language",
        "Hyper Tabular Markup Language",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "ansindex": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Which of the following tag is used to mark a beginning of paragraph ?",
      "options": [
        "<TD>",
        "<br>",
        "<P>",
        "<TR>"
      ],
      "answer": "C",
      "ansindex": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "From which tag descriptive list starts ?",
      "options": [
        "<LL>",
        "<DD>",
        "<DL>",
        "<DS>"
      ],
      "answer": "C",
      "ansindex": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Correct HTML tag for the largest heading is",
      "options": [
        "<head>",
        "<h6>",
        "<heading>",
        "<h1>"
      ],
      "answer": "D",
      "ansindex": 3
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "The attribute of <form> tag",
      "options": [
        "Method",
        "Action",
        "Both (a)&(b)",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": "C",
      "ansindex": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Markup tags tell the web browser",
      "options": [
        "How to organise the page",
        "How to display the page",
        "How to display message box on page",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "ansindex": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "www is based on which model?",
      "options": [
        "Local-server",
        "Client-server",
        "3-tier",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "ansindex": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "What are Empty elements and is it valid?",
      "options": [
        "No, there is no such terms as Empty Element",
        "Empty elements are element with no data",
        "No, it is not valid to use Empty Element",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "ansindex": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Which of the following attributes of text box control allow to limit the maximum character?",
      "options": [
        "size",
        "len",
        "maxlength",
        "all of these"
      ],
      "answer": "C",
      "ansindex": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Web pages starts with which of the following tag?",
      "options": [
        "<Body>",
        "<Title>",
        "<HTML>",
        "<Form>"
      ],
      "answer": "C",
      "ansindex": 2
    }
  ],
  "answers": []
}